[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 12]
♪ Watch me leap forward ♪
♪ Fall and rise ♪
♪ I am brave ♪
♪ You will find, find your way ♪
This is for you.
♪ Win or lose ♪
♪ I'm fighting through to the end ♪
♪ Just to breathe again ♪
This is the place.
Guys,
please stop what you're doing.
Today,
we have a new member joining our publicity team,
Song Baiwei.
She has prepared a
charity sale and fundraising plan.
Let's listen to what she has to say.
Welcome! Great! Welcome!
Here's the thing.
Previously,
I thought of a plan.
Our country is in a time of crisis.
You can take a look first.
Since I am good at painting,
I plan to hold a charity sale.
Baiwei.
Go on.
Your painting is in the newspaper again. Look!
It's in the newspaper!
That's great!
Let me see.
What does it say?
This is good.
Yeah.
Commander Ning compensates a fallen subordinate
and adopts his orphaned daughter.
Let's see.
Go over there.
Let's go. Let's go.
Let's appreciate it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Why aren't you heading home to rest?
Didn't you say
that recently
you've been driving the cinema boss to and from work
just to get us this activity room?
Aren't you tired?
I'm not tired.
Watching you write is my way of resting.
Baiwei,
let's go watch a movie tomorrow.
I'm not going.
Why?
Just the two of us watching a movie...
that's so boring.
If you're so capable,
invite everyone to go.
Tomorrow I'm treating everyone to a movie!
Great!
That's wonderful!
Dad...
Go home right now.
Not now.
I'll go back when I'm done here.
What are you busy with?
Hanging out with these people
in this place,
doing all this nonsense every day!
Go home!
You are getting engaged to Miss Chen next month.
Never touch any of this again.
Who is this?
The president of Zhiyuan Chamber of Commerce.
I can't believe he's Lin's father.
Dad,
do you know how the Chen family
made their fortune?
Smuggling medicines
and profiteering from the national crisis!
You...
And also,
the family business you want me to inherit...
the textile mills, grain stores, and pawnshops...
you hoard supplies
and tripled the price of rice!
Did you think I didn't know?
How dare you!
Mr. Lin, this is an activity room.
It's not a place for you to throw your weight around
and handle family matters.
Who do you think you are?
Are you okay, Lin Huai?
How dare you lecture me!
I am his friend,
and also one of "these people" you just mentioned.
Since you're here
and publicly insulted us,
you should at least know
what we actually do here.
This is our schedule for the week.
What we spread every day
are messages about saving our nation.
We raise funds for the soldiers
on the front lines who lack food and clothing.
It's where your medicine
and rice should have gone.
As for your son,
Lin Huai,
he is crying out for those who starved to death
and those who froze to death.
You should thank him.
He runs around
to save the country from peril.
He has been accumulating virtue for your Lin family.
I just don't know
if it can keep up with the speed at which you lose it.
You!
Lin Huai!
Every cent you spend
belongs to the Lin family.
Young Master, what are you doing?
Please stop!
Sir,
the Young Master is still young
and childish.
Please calm down.
You ungrateful son!
What are you doing?
You're right.
I've been spending
the dirty money you made.
Right now, I don't have
a single cent from the Lin family.
And not a single thing
bears the Lin family name.
From now on,
the Lin family and I
are completely through.
Baiwei, let's go.
Young Master.
Lin Huai!
If you walk away today,
don't ever come back!
So?
How do I look?
I'm sorry.
Not bad.
Way better than your
rich kid clothes.
You bet.
I bought this with the money
from pulling Miss Baiwei's rickshaw.
It feels amazing to wear it.
Stop messing around.
You know,
you're pretty and sweet,
and...
you really know how to curse people out.
In my whole life,
I've never seen my dad so speechless.
Is that a compliment?
Obviously.
You've got all three.
How rare.
♪ Do you see me? ♪
♪ Do you hear me? ♪
♪ Just take a step ♪
♪ And try to see another way ♪
♪ Do you see me? ♪
♪ Do you hear me? ♪
♪ Just take a step ♪
♪ And try to see another day ♪
♪ Another hero emerges ♪
Baiwei.
What's wrong?
♪ Another hero emerges ♪
♪ To save the day ♪
It's snowing hard.
Let's go.
♪ Do you see me? ♪
♪ Do you hear me? ♪
♪ Just take a step ♪
♪ Don't let me down ♪
♪ Do you see me? ♪
♪ Do you hear me? ♪
♪ Just take a step ♪
♪ Don't let me down ♪
Awesome!
Just in time for the premiere.
I gotta get back to work.
Let's leave together tonight.
Okay.
Look at this.
Please.
Drawing is exhausting.
Look at me.
Give me a smile.
Lin Huai,
how old are you?
My pen.
I need to draw.
Call me brother,
call me brother and it's yours.
Give it back.
Then you have to draw for me.
Call me brother and I will.
Or no pen for you.
In your dreams!
Hey!
I have a deadline!
Lin Huai,
aren't you
a bit childish?
Baiwei,
I really love you.
I love you so much.
My life
was empty and dull.
But falling in love with you
made it shine.
I can't promise you a lifetime of peace,
instead, I'm begging you.
Begging you to grant me
this endless honor.
Please marry me.
Let me stay by your side
lifetime after lifetime.
Marry him!
Look.
This is our marriage certificate from back then.
Do you really not remember?
No, I don't.
You show up here today
with some photos
and a video,
make up some century-old story,
and expect me to believe
that we are Song Baiwei and Lin Huai from a century ago?
It's absurd.
I'm sorry.
I'm not feeling well.
You should leave.
Wait.
I never once mentioned
the name Song Baiwei.
You remember.
You remember everything, don't you?
Why are you pretending not to know me?
We've known each other for so long.
Why...
Tell me.
Lin Huai...
About that marriage certificate you gave me...
I thought it over.
Let's get through the fundraiser first.
It's okay.
When all this is over,
I'll wait for your answer.
Why is the rain getting so heavy?
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
Wait for me here.
So tragic.
What happened?
Who would do this?
Does anyone know him?
No one's even here for his body.
Yeah.
Poor guy.
Exactly.
He must've crossed the wrong people
for this to happen.
Lin Huai.
Lin Huai!
Help!
Somebody help!
Lin Huai!
Help!
Get a doctor!
Lin Huai!
Let's get you to a hospital.
Let's get to a hospital.
Lin Huai, don't...
Don't die on me.
Please don't die.
Lin Huai!
The Lin Huai in my memory
died on the street just like that.
He died at the age of twenty.
His body was cold.
He never woke up again.
Why are you pretending not to know me?
We've known each other for so long.
Why...
Tell me.
Lin Huai.
Director Lin.